剧情回顾
Previously on "Lost"...
Michael
我找到他们了...其他人
I found them...the others.
我看到一个
I saw one.
我跟着他去了他们的营地
I followed himback to their camp.
他们住在帐篷里...帆布帐篷和圆顶帐篷
They live in tents. canvas tents and...and teepees.
他们吃腌鱼  他们的条件不如我们
They eat dried fish. They're worse off than we are.
他们有一个舱子
they have a hatch.
整天整夜都有人守卫
They keep it guarded 24/7,
两个守卫  两把枪  我只看到两把
two guards, two guns, and two guns is all I saw.
Michael?
所以我回来告诉你
So I came back to tell you.
你看到Walt了么?
Did you see walt?
没有
No.
但我知道他在那
But I know he's there.
一旦我恢复体力...
As soon as I getmy strength back...
我会带你们去那里的
i will take us back there,
然后带回我的孩子
and we are gonna get my boy back.
13天前
嘿  John  John
hey, John. John.
我希望我能借把枪
I was hoping I could borrowone of these guns.
这应该是个秘密吧?
Is this supposed to bea secret?
Jack睡着了
Jack's asleep.
要再练练么?
More target practice?
是的  你知道...我想保持状态
Yeah, well, you know...just wanna stay sharp.
你有约?
You got a date?
不是  老习惯了
No. Old habits, you know.
-好了  拿去吧   -谢谢  伙计
-Yes, I do.  -Thanks, man.
我能拿几包弹药么?
Hey, can I just get a coupleof these bullets?
我保证不会...该死  抱歉
I promise I won't...ah,damn! I'm sorry.
-不  没事  我来好了  -抱歉
-No, that's all right. I got it.  -I'm sorry.
拜托  你在哪?
Come on. Where are you?
你好么?
You okay?
很好  没时间了  你要来了么?
ok, no time, come soon?
我准备好了  马上来了  你说在北面的哪?
I'm ready, coming now, you said north north where?
他们带走我的时候  在海滩边上有个中间有孔的巨石
when they take me out,there's huge rocks with a big hole in the middle by the beach.
你看到就知道了
you'll know when you see
好的  我来了
it's gonna be okay,I'm coming
我来了  Walt
I'm coming, Walt.
John
别动
Stay in there.
-别动  -Michael  你在...
-Stay...  -Michael, what are you?
在那别动  Jack
Stay in there, Jack!
不管发生了什么...
Hey, whatever's going on...
我都要去找我儿子  我要找我儿子
Look, I'm going after my son. I'm going after my son
没人可以阻拦我  明白么?
and nobody is going to stop me, OK?
那是我的权利  一个父亲的权利
That is my right. That is a father's right.
今天
你在这干嘛?
What are you doing out here?
没什么  呼吸点新鲜空气
Nothing. Just getting some air.
来吧  我们谈谈
Come on. We should talk.
一共有几把?
How many?
来复枪和手枪?  一共11把
Rifles and pistols? Eleven total.
-没有了?  -没有了
-That's it?  -That's it.
你别忘了  他们从我们这拿走了五把
They took five of them right off us.
去他们营地要多久?
How long to get to their camp?
现在就走  快的话...明天午夜可以到
We leave now, move fast, middle of the night tomorrow.
听着  他们还不知道他们被我发现了
They have no idea I know where they are.
他们不会有准备的 所以我们带上枪就可以走了
They won't be expecting us. So we get the guns and we go.
-现在就走  就我们五个   -不不  五个不够
-Right now, just the five of us.  -No. Five's not enough.
你说他们至少有20个人 他们拿走了我们的枪
You said there's at least 20 of them with our guns.
而且我们还不确定你看到的是不是...
We're not sure if what you saw was...
我知道我看到了什么
Hey, I know what I saw.
我们带太多的人  他们就会知道我们来了
We take too many people, they'll hear us coming.
我不会带一支军队横穿这个岛的  Jack
I'm not taking a damn army across the island.
Michael  你肯定你可以
Sure you're in the best place
为我们这些在场的人作决定么?
to be making decisions now?
你有儿子么  Jack?
You got a son, Jack?
他们死了
They're dead.
Ana Lucia和Libby死了
Ana Lucia and Libby are dead.
我是说  我们还没安葬他们
I mean, we haven't even buried them yet.
我和你处理Libby的事  好么?
Me and you'll take Libby, OK?
-你可以...  -恩  当然
-Can you?  -Yeah. Of course.
-Sawyer  可以么?  -好的
-Sawyer, would you?  -Yeah.
你得呆在这
You should stay here.
我们今晚葬了他们  然后...
We'll bury them tonight...
我们再打算接下去怎么办
then we'll figure out what's next.
迷 失
第二季 第二十二集
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
13天前
把手举起来
Put your hands up.
举起手来
Put them up.
别动
Don't move.
放松点  伙计  我没动
Relax, buddy. I ain't moving.
-你为什么不...  -闭嘴
-Why don't you just put that?  -Shut up.
你是Walt的爸爸  不是么?
You're Walt's old man, aren't you?
什么?
What?
你在干什么?  我们需要他
What are you doing? We need him.
把他套起来
Bag him, quick.
他的朋友就在我们后面
His friends are right behind us.
今天
你好
Hello.
我没听见你进来  伙计
I didn't hear you come in, man.
我把鞋子放外面了
I left my shoes outside.
它们很脏
They were muddy.
你找到他了么?  Henry
Did you find him? Henry?
没有
No.
我听说你是个牧师
I hear you're a priest.
是的
Yes.
那我猜你是相信有地狱了
Guess you believe in hell, then.
我为英格兰的一个小教区做过一段时间
For a brief time, I served in a small parish in England.
每个周日集会后
Every Sunday after Mass
我都会看到一个小男孩等在教堂的后面
I would see a young boy waiting at the back of the church.
然后有一天  他向我忏悔
And then, one day, the boy confessed to me
他用铁铲把他的狗打死了
that he had beaten his dog to death with a shovel.
他说那条狗在咬她妹妹的屁股
And he said the dog had bitten his baby sister on the cheek
他得保护她
and he needed to protect her.
他想知道他会不会为这事而入地狱
And he wanted to know whether he would go to hell for this.
我告诉他说上帝会理解的
I told him that God would understand.
他会被宽恕的...
That he would be forgiven
就像他现在感到难过一样
as long as he was sorry.
但是这个男孩不在乎宽恕
But the boy did not care about forgiveness.
他只是害怕如果他真的入了地狱...
He was only afraid that if he did go to hell
那条狗会在那等他
that dog would be there waiting for him.
你还好吧?
You all right?
我没事
Yeah.
我正要回去再给你查查
I was coming back to check on you.
好的  伙计
Yeah, man.
我得离开那
I had to get out of there.
因为...
I just...
我得带回我的孩子
I have to get my son back.
我们会帮你的  Michael
We're gonna help you do that, Michael.
必须要按我说的做  伙计
It's gotta be the way I said, man.
就我们五个
Just the five of us.
否则就不行了  不行了
Otherwise it won't work. It won't work.
我保证  我们会想出办法的
We're gonna figure that out.
我已经有一个办法了
I have already figured it out.
就是这些知道这事的人
It's gotta be just the people who already know.
你  我  Kate  Sawyer  Hurley  就这样
You, me, Kate, Sawyer, Hurley. That's it.
其他的人...会使我的处境更加危险
Anybody else...Look, it puts him in more danger.
你别乱定主意了
You don't get to decide this.
是我儿子的事  由我来决定
It's my son. It's my call.
事情只能是这样的
And that's the way it has to be.
那就这样吧
Then that's the way it'll be.
Hey, Aaron.
大家伙
Hey, big guy.
有看到Eko么?
Have you seen Eko?
没有
No.
你知道  我们在建一座教堂
You know, we're building a church.
你有事么  Charlie?
Is there something you want, Charlie?
是的
Yeah.
我在降落伞那找到了这个
I found something in the pallet
我想你会用得到
I thought you might need.
疫苗?
Vaccine?
我不知道我们要疫苗来做什么
I don't know what we need vaccine for
但我想如果有人需要的话
but if anyone should have it
只有你和你的孩子了
you and the baby should.
没事的  这是...
It's all right.
这是空气注射器
It's a pneumatic injector.
你只要...
You just
你把它插进你的腿里  然后...
put it into your leg, and...
疫苗就进去了
It goes right in.
一点都不痛  真的
Quite painless, really.
你好像很在行
You seem to know a lot about it.
我试过了
I tried it.
给你和你孩子前我想确保它没问题
I wanted to make sure it was safe before giving it to you and the baby.
你感觉怎样?  我是说  它有效么?
how do you feel? I mean, did it do anything?
它...它有效么?
What did it do?
我不知道  我感觉很好
I don't know. I feel fine.
反正这说了
Anyway, it says
你应该每隔九天注射一次
you're supposed to give yourself a shot every nine days.
好么?  这里的量足够
All right? So, I mean, there's enough here
你和你的孩子用一段时间了
for you and the baby for a while.
就这些了
That's it.
好了
All right
-我把它放在...  -好的
-I'll put it...  -Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Welcome.
我要给他吃东西了  所以...
I should really feed him.
好的  Claire?
Yeah. Hey, Claire
你想也许我和你...我想...
do you think maybe you and I could?
天哪
Oh, my God.
Michael回来了
Michael's back.
Michael?
是Michael
Look, there's Michael!
恩  很好很好  见到你很高兴
Uh, yeah, yeah. It's good to see you, too.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
是的  我...只是...
Yeah. I'm...
我很好
I'm fine.
是谁?
Who?
Ana Lucia和Libby
Ana Lucia and Libby.
发生了什么事?
What happened to them?
他们被杀了
They were murdered.
13天前
好啊  Michael
Hey, there, Michael.
别跟自己较劲了
Not gonna hold that against you.
我带走了你的孩子  这样就算扯平了  别再这么做了好吧?
Fair's fair. I took your boy. But don't do that again, OK?
他在哪?  你这狗娘养的
Where is he, you son of a bitch?
看看我找到了谁  她一直跟着她的朋友
Hey, looky what I found. She was following her friends.
跟在我们后面半公里处
They're about half a click behind us.
你一旦发出声音...
You make one sound...
你就永远看不到你的儿子了
you'll never see your boy again.
塞住他
Gag him.
把火把准备好
Get ready with the torches.
我要和她的朋友们谈谈
I'm gonna go talk to her people.
-我想我们最好回去  -什么?
-I think we'd better head back.  -What?
-快找痕迹吧  John  -我找不到了
-Find the trail, John.  -I've lost it.
你不是找不到  你只是不想找到他
You don't just lose a trail. You just don't want to find him.
就是这样  Jack
That's right.
我一路穿过丛林
I've been running through the jungle
追着枪声而来
toward the sound of gunfire
因为我一点也不在乎Michael
because I don't care about Michael.
你知道我们现在就回头会发生什么么?
You know what happens if we turn around and go back?
我们就再也见不到他了 全是因为我们
We're never gonna see him again. And that's gonna be on us.
因为你和我
On you and on me.
你说得很对  Jack
You're exactly right, Jack.
你是谁?
Who are you?
他就是在救生筏上开枪打我的人
He's the son of a bitch that shot me on the raft.
干吗不把枪放下呢?
Why don't you point the gun down?
没事的  他只是在传达信息
It's OK. He's just delivering a message.
他得吓吓你的朋友
He has to scare your friends to do it.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
你不相信什么?
You don't believe what?
我认为我们的人比你们的多
I think there's more of us than there are of you.
这个理论很有趣
That's an interesting theory.
亮火把
Light them up!
把武器给我  转身  回去吧
Give me your weapons, turn around, go home.
不
No.
我本不想这样的
I hoped it wouldn't come to this.
把她带上来  Alex
Bring her out, Alex.
你去吧
Go on.
-你...  -拜托  Alex
-You.  -Come on, Alex.
求你了
Please?
我们走  快快
Let's go. Up. Up.
Claire还好吧?
Is Claire OK?
她的孩子生了么?  没事吧?
Did she have the baby? Is it OK?
是男的还是女的?
Is it a boy or a girl?
就像我说的  她很好奇...
Like I said, curiosity.
我和你还没完  Zeke
You and me ain't done, Zeke.
他的朋友们回去了
His friends are going home.
打晕他
Divvy them up.
对不起
Sorry.
今天
看见了么  医生
Hey. What do you say, Doc?
我认为爱尔兰人只在有人死了的时候才喝酒
And here I was thinking the Irish drink when somebody dies.
我不是爱尔兰人
I'm not Irish.
我也不是
Neither am I.
丛林里发生了什么?
So what happened out there in the jungle?
就像他说的一样  他找到了营地...
Exactly what he said. He found the camp...
我不是在说Mike  你和那个小妞...
I ain't talking about Mike. You and Freckles.
在你找到他前  你们消失了整整一晚上
Before you found him. You were gone all night.
我们被网住了
We got caught in a net.
那是什么意思?
What's the hell's that supposed to mean?
那说明我们被网住了
It means we got caught in a net.
就像这些天他们所说的一样?
That what they're calling it these days?
是真的么?  Henry逃了?
Is it true? Henry is gone?
是的
Yeah.
有人在追他么?
Who's going after him?
Locke和Eko在半夜里去追了
Locke and Eko went in the night.
但是到现在还没看到他们回来
We ain't seen either of them since.
这些是枪  对吧? 拿来做什么?
Those are the guns? What are you doing with them?
你认为呢?  该是结束一切的时候了
What do you think we're doing? It's time to finish this.
-你们什么时候动身?  -天亮就走
-When do we leave?  -In the morning.
你不用去  Sayid
You're not coming, Sayid.
什么?
Excuse me?
Michael不想人太多... 就我  Kate  Hurley 和...
Michael wants to keep it small. Me, Kate, Hurley
和他
and him.
没错  "他"说连长袜子皮皮和那见鬼的葡萄猩猩
Well even though Pippi Longstocking and the damned Grape Ape
都能成为这次该死行动的理想候选人
are ideal candidates for The Dirty Dozen
我看干吗不带上Sayid呢
we might wanna bring the Red Beret.
都由Michael说了算  他知道我们要去哪
It's Michael's call. He knows where we're going.
不由他说了算  Jack  我们说了算
It is not his call, Jack. It's ours.
欢迎加入
Welcome aboard.
那么...你半夜醒来
So... you wake up in the middle of the night
抓起你的耶稣棒然后跑进丛林
grab your Jesus stick, and race off into the jungle.
没叫我  也没留字条
You don't call, you don't write...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我有事要做
I had work to do.
好的好的
Right. Yeah.
Charlie  能帮我个忙么?
Charlie, would you do me a favor?
我希望你能把我在海滩上的东西带来
I was hoping you could bring my things from the beach here.
为什么?
What for?
你要搬来这住?
You moving in here?
你想要你自己的小单人间?
Fancy yourself a little bachelor pad?
是的  我要搬到这里来
Yes, I am moving in here.
那么教堂怎么办?
what about the church?
我说我们要一起建的  伙计
You said we were supposed to be building it together.
我现在有其他事要做了
I am supposed to do something different now.
我应该怎么办?
And what am I supposed to do?
把我的东西带来
Bring me my things.
你自己去拿吧
ring your own things.
Charlie  拜托
Charlie, please.
你最好快点去拿  伙计
You'd better leg it, mate.
表可不会停下来等你
Clock's ticking.
有好消息要告诉你
Got some good news for you.
阿拉伯船长也加入我们了
Captain Arab's in, too.
日出时出发
Cavalry rides at sunrise.
你告诉了Sayid?
You told Sayid?
是的  我和Sayid说了
Yeah, I told Sayid.
你不能说的
You shouldn't have done that.
是么  我很抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
我只是觉得  如果我们是去打仗
I figured if we're going to war
我们需要一个参加过战争的人
we'd want the one guy who's been in a war.
这有问题么?
That a problem?
恩  没有
No.
没有问题
It's not a problem.
那么不就行了
All right, then.
11天前
放开我
Get off of me.
你有问题么  Michael?
You got a problem, Michael?
你们逼着我走了一天一夜没有休息了
You march me a day and night without any rest, yeah.
我太累了
My problem is I'm tired.
我还想把你打晕了扛着走的
I'd offer to knock you out and carry you
但是我们到了
but we're here.
把他放到那去
Put him right over here.
告诉他我们到了
Tell her we're here.
可能会有点疼
I can't promise this won't hurt.
那是... 该死
What the? Ow! Damn it.
放松点  只是取点血
Relax. Just taking some blood.
取血干什么?  你们是谁?
Taking some blood? For what? Who are you people?
我儿子在哪?
Where's my son?
好了
That's it. All done.
看看结果如何了
See you in the funny pages.
你好  Micheal
Hello, Michael.
我儿子在哪?
Where's my son?
我叫Klugh
My name is Miss Klugh.
我希望你能回答我几个问题...
I was hoping you might help me answer some questions.
是关于Walt的
About Walt.
他在哪?
Where is he?
他是你的亲生儿子么?
Is he your biological son?
什么?
What?
你是他父亲么?
Are you his father?
他几岁开始说话的?
How old was he when he started speaking?
我...他...
I... He...
他成长过程中有生病么?  头痛?
Did he have any illnesses growing up? Headaches?
经常性昏迷?
Fainting spells?
什么?  没有
What? No.
我不知...我不在那  他离我半个地球远
I don't... I wasn't there. He was halfway around the world.
你为什么问我这些?
Why are you asking me?
Walt有没曾经出现在不可能出现的地方?
Did Walt ever appear in a place he wasn't supposed to be?
你说他离你有半个地球远  但是...
You say he was halfway around the world
-你有看见...  -我要我的儿子
-but did you see...  -I want my son.
你马上把他带来见我
You bring him to me right now.
我要见我儿子
I wanna see my boy.
对于一个如此想要回自己儿子的人来说...
For someone who wants his son back so badly
你对他并不是太了解  Michael
you don't seem to know much about him, Michael.
今天
你不用去
You're not coming.
欢迎回来  Michael
Welcome back, Michael.
听着  我知道Sawyer和你说了  好了
Look, I know Sawyer told you.
但是  这样不行的
But it's not gonna work.
你不能去
You're not coming.
为什么我不能去?
And why is it that I'm not coming?
因为你是要去追那个逃跑的人
Because you're going after the guy who escaped
而我是要去找我儿子
and I'm going after my son.
你是不是说我的报复心胜过对于Walt安全的担心?
Are you implying I'd let a desire for revenge compromise Walt's safety?
我是说由我来决定谁去谁留下
I'm implying that I decide who stays and who goes
你留下
and you stay.
我知道你想帮忙  是么?
I know you wanna help, right?
但是我需要按我的方式来做
But I gotta do this my way.
当然
Of course.
祝你好运  Michael
Good luck, Michael.
好的  谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
该死的
Bloody hell.
你没开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding me?
有人让你这么做的么?
Did someone put you up to this?
Vincent?
你们应该早就回来的
You were supposed to come right back.
你们整夜都在丛林里  怎么了?
You were out all night. What happened?
我们无法发现Henry的行踪
We were unable to find Henry's trail.
是的  我知道了
Yeah, I got that.
Lock在哪?
Where's Locke?
我不知道
I do not know.
我们在日落时安葬Ana Lucia和Libby
We're burying Ana Lucia and Libby at sunset.
谢谢
Thank you.
我以我自己的方式来悼念他们
I will mourn them in my own way.
由谁来说?
Who's gonna talk?
什么?
What?
在葬礼上
At the funeral.
由谁来说?
Who's gonna talk?
我肯定Hurley想说些和Libby有关的
I'm sure Hurley'll wanna say something about Libby.
我甚至不知道她的姓
I never even knew her last name.
Ana Lucia
她姓Cortez
It was Cortez.
Cortez
我知道了
Well, there you go.
我和她干过了
I screwed her.
什么?
What?
她就是这么拿走我的枪的
It's how she got my gun. Ana.
她主动要和我来的
She jumped me.
我们被网住了
We got caught in a net.
你为什么告诉我这些  Sawyer?
Why are you telling me this?
因为你是唯一可以算作我朋友的人  医生
Because you're about the closest thing I got to a friend, Doc.
因为她死了
And because she's gone.
至少我们可以去杀几个人了
at least now we get to kill somebody.
Jack和你说过我们的计划了么?
Jack fill you in on the plan?
什么计划?
What plan?
我们明早动身
We're leaving first thing tomorrow.
横穿岛屿到他们营地去
Back across the island to their camp.
好的
OK.
你呢  伙计?  你一起来么?
And what about you, man? You coming with us?
为什么我要去?
Why would I wanna go?
因为他们杀了她
Because they killed her.
Michael  别说了
Michael, come on.
你说呢  Hugo?
What do you say, Hugo?
对于Walt我很抱歉  伙计 但是我不去
I'm sorry about Walt, dude, but I'm not coming.
-你对不起什么...  -Michael
-You're sorry about...  -Michael.
3天前
该吃饭了
Dinnertime.
你什么时候动手?
When are you gonna do it?
动手干嘛?
When am I going to do what?
杀了我
Kill me.
我看到了你们住哪
I've seen where you live.
我知道怎么来这
I know how to get here.
你一直在问我问题
You have been asking me questions
我都答不上来
I don't know the answers to for a week.
我甚至不能肯定我儿子还活着  而且...
I don't even think my son is alive.
他还活着  Michael
He is alive, Michael.
他现在就站在外面
He's standing outside right now.
你认为我是傻子么?
What, do you think I'm stupid?
你来这里后发生了一些事情  Michael
There's been a development since you came here, Michael.
一个我们的人被你们抓了
One of our people was captured by yours.
那就去把他救回来啊
So go get him back.
我们做不到
We can't do that.
但是你可以
But you can.
如果你做到了...
And, if you do...
我们就放了你和Walt
we'll let you and Walt go free.
我要见我儿子
I want to see my son.
Michael...
我要见他
I want to see him.
如果他在外面  你就带他进来
If he is out there, you bring him in.
你马上带他进来
You bring him in here right now.
哨兵
Pickett.
你们有三分钟时间
You have three minutes.
Walt
爸爸
Dad.
放开他
Let him go.
-放开他  马上放开他   -爸爸  不要
-Let him go. Get your hands off him right now.  -Dad, don't.
你还好么?
Are you OK?
是的
Yeah.
他们有伤害你么?
Are you... Did they hurt you?
他们拿我做试验
They make me take tests.
他们拿你做什么?
They make you what?
我们不谈那个
We're not gonna talk about that.
Vincent还好么?
How's Vincent?
Vincent...它很好
Vincent's...He's great.
它很好  它很想你
He's great. He misses you.
别怕  伙计
Hey, don't be scared, man.
别害怕
Don't be scared.
马上就会没事的  好么?
It's gonna be over real soon.
我会带你离开这里的  好么?
I'm gonna get you out.
他们不像他们所说的...
They're not who they say they are.
你想我再把你关进那个房间么?
Want me to put you in the room?
假装?  假装什么?
Pretending? Pretending what?
好了  就这样了
OK, that's it. We're done.
不不不不  等等  嘿  等等
No, wait. Hey, wait, wait.
过来  Walt  等等  过来  等等
Come here, Walt. Wait,
-过来  -爸爸
-come here.  -Dad
别离开我  帮帮我 求你了  别离开我
don't leave me. Help me, please. Don't leave me.
我不会的  伙计  我会把你带走的  好么?
I won't, man. I'm gonna get you out of here, OK?
我保证
I promise you.
-我会把你从这里带走的  -爸爸  爸爸
-I will get you out.  -Dad! Dad!
-放开他  放开他  -我爱你
-Let him go! Walt, wait! Let go of him!  -I love you!
-Walt  我会把你带走的   -我爱你
-Walt, I'm gonna get you out of here.  -I love you!
-我也爱你  Walt  -放开我  放开我
-I love you too, Walt.  -Put me down! Let me go!
-我会把你带走的   -爸爸
-I'll get you...  -Dad!
在你放了我们的人之后
After you release our man
我还要你做些事
I'm gonna need you to do something else.
随便你
I'll do it. I'll do whatever you want.
我写了四个名字...四个你朋友的名字
I'm writing four names down. Four of your friends.
我们要你带他们来这
We need you to bring them here.
你只需要带这四个人  Michael
You have to bring only these four people, Michael.
就他们
Just them.
如果你不能把名单上的四个人都带来...
If you don't bring all the people on the list...
你永远也见不到Walt了
you'll never see Walt again.
好的  好的
OK. OK. OK.
你听懂了么  Michael?
Do you understand, Michael?
我该怎么和他们说?
Yes. What do I tell them?
这没关系
Doesn't matter.
编一个故事
Make up a story.
他们无论听你说什么都会怒火冲天的
They'll be angry enough to believe whatever you say.
James Ford是谁?
Who's James Ford?
就是你知道的Sawyer
You know him as Sawyer.
你认识其他的人么?
You know the rest of them?
是的
Yeah.
我知道他们
I know them.
如果我做了这些...
If I do all this...
如果我照你说的做了...
If I do what you say.
你就可以带回你的孩子
You'll get your son back...
你们就都自由了
and you both go free.
我还要一艘船
And I want the boat.
当飞机坠毁时  我正在去洛杉矶安葬我父亲的路上
When the plane crashed, I was on my way to Los Angeles to bury my dad.
我很难过
I'm sorry to hear that.
现在看起来好像过去很久了
It seems like such a long time ago now.
我本来要从机场直接去墓地的 但是...
I was gonna go right from the airport to the cemetery, but...
我不知道我该说些什么
I had no idea what I was gonna say.
现在又是这种时候了
And here we are again
我觉得Michael向他们妥协了
I think Michael has been compromised.
我们继续走  Jack
Let's keep walking, Jack.
你说妥协是什么意思?
What do you mean, compromised?
他的作为不像是一个讲真话的人
His actions are not those of a man telling the truth.
他为什么要向我们撒谎?
Why would he lie to us?
因为我相信一个父亲会为了孩子而做一切
Because I believe a father would do anything for his son.
因为我相信Henry可能是Michael放走的
Because I believe that Michael may have freed Henry,
并且我相信他要带你们去一个陷阱
and because I believe he's leading you into a trap.
你相信的太多了  Sayid
You believe a lot, Sayid.
我还相信Henry是他们中的一员
And I also believed that Henry was one of them.
好吧  我们去和他谈谈
All right. Let's go talk to him.
不  他必须继续以为他还掌控着大局
No. He must believe he's in control.
我们为什么要这么做?
Why the hell would we wanna do that?
这样我们就能取得主动了
So we can create an advantage.
怎么做?
How?
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
但是我们还有一晚可以想办法
But we have one more night to figure that out.
Ana Lucia Cortez 是...
Ana Lucia Cortez was...
在我们坠机前  她是一个警察
Before we crashed, she was a police officer.
我想她在这里的日子并不好过
I don't think it was easy for her being here
但是我想她是尽力了
but I think she did the best she could.
她是一个话很少的人
She was a woman of few words
我会以你为榜样的
and I'm gonna follow her example.
安息吧  Ana
Rest in peace, Ana.
Libby 是...
Libby was...
她是...
She was...
Libby是一个心理医生
Libby was a psychologist.
或是一个...精神病医生
Or a psychiatrist.
二者其一
One of those. Either way,
她可能帮助过许多人
she probably helped a lot of people.
她帮助过我
She helped me.
她是我的朋友
She was my friend.
发生这种事对她来说是不公平的  绝对不
It's not fair that this happened to her. It's not.
我和你一起去
I'm going with you.
再见  Libby
Goodbye, Libby.
船
Boat.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====